Office of the President Records UA001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Lawrence Seldon Bacow administrative records and related papers, 1835 -- 2014; 2001 -- 2011; UA001.018; 32.2 Linear Feet; 3 Artifact(s); 32 Digital Object(s)
  - Subject files, 1992 -- 2014; UA001.018.001; 14.4 Linear Feet; 12 Digital Object(s)
    - College Sports Project, 2005 -- 2007; UA001.018.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
      - College Sports Project - Data Report, 2005 -- 2007; UA001.018.001.003.00010.00003
    - Colonial Group Presidents, 2010; UA001.018.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
    - Commencement 1987, UA001.005376 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Commencement 1995, 1995 -- 2001; UA001.005377 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Commencement 2003, UA001.005378 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Commencement 2004, UA001.005379 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Commencement 2005, UA001.005380 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Commencement 2006, UA001.005381 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Commencement [binder 1 of 2], 2007; UA001.018.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
    - Commencement [binder 2 of 2], 2007; UA001.018.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
    - Commencement 2011, UA001.005382 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Commencement 2011 Miscellaneous photos, UA001.005383 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Commission on International Education, 2002; UA001.018.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
    - Communications/News Group, 2002 -- 2005; UA001.018.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
    - Community Appeal, 2001 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
    - Community Day - 8th Annual, 2009 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
    - Community Day, 2003; UA001.018.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    - Community Day, 2004; UA001.018.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
    - Community Relations - Boston, 2002 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
    - Community Relations - Medford, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
    - Community Relations - Somerville [1 of 2], 2004 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
    - Community Relations - Somerville [2 of 2], 2001 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
    - Complaints, 1999 -- 2002; UA001.018.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
    - Complaint Letters, 2002 -- 2003; UA001.018.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
    - Complaints, 2003 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
    - Complaints, 2005; UA001.018.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
    - Condolences, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
    - Congratulatory Letters, 2002 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
    - Consultation Dinners, 2006; UA001.018.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
    - Counseling Center, 2003 -- 2005; UA001.005384 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 2009 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
    - Council for Higher Education 10th Anniversary Commission, 2006 -- 2007; UA001.018.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
    - Greg Crane, 2001 -- 2002; UA001.018.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
    - Crisis Communications, 2007; UA001.018.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
    - Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine, 2010 -- 2011; UA001.005385 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - David D'Alessandro, 2002 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
    - Davis United World College Scholars, 2004 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Davis United World College Scholars, 2011; UA001.005386 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - DayCare Center, 2008; UA001.018.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
    - Debate Society, 2003; UA001.018.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
    - Deep Underground Science and Engineering Laboratory DUSEL, 2010 -- 2011; UA001.005387 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Dental School of Medicine, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.005388 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Development, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
    - John DiBiaggio, 2001 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
    - DILES Event, 2005; UA001.018.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
    - Kristine Dillon, 2002; UA001.018.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
    - Diversity, 1999 -- 2010; UA001.005389 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Drama and Dance, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
    - DREU, 2005; UA001.018.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
    - Drexel Survey, 2003; UA001.018.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
    - Dreyfus Foundation Camille and Henry, 2011; UA001.005390 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Dutko Group, LLC, 2001 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
    - Bob Dylan, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
    - Eagle Scout Award, 2001; UA001.018.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
    - Education Department, 2009; UA001.018.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
    - EDUCAUSE Network Guidelines, 2003; UA001.018.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
    - Eliot-Pearson Department of Child Development, 2007; UA001.018.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
      - Inside Stories from the Tufts Literary Corps, 2007; UA001.018.001.004.00016.00001 (Box 4)
        Video created by Yeu Jin Yoon
        DVDs
    - Employee Recognition, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
    - Engineering, 1999 -- 2008; UA001.005391 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Engineering Accreditation, 1999 -- 2010; UA001.005392 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - English as Second Language (ESL), 2005; UA001.018.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
    - Entrepreneurship Conference, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 2006; UA001.018.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
    - Equestrian Team, 2002; UA001.018.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
    - Everett Power Project, 2006; UA001.018.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
    - Faculty Awards/Nominations, 2011; UA001.018.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
    - Faculty Letters, 2010; UA001.018.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
    - Faculty Proposals, 2010; UA001.018.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
    - Faculty Sabbatical, 2003; UA001.018.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
    - Fares Lecture, 2005; UA001.018.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
    - Faculty Retention, 2001; UA001.018.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
    - Fares Lecture, 2010; UA001.018.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
    - Fares Lecture- Tony Blair, 2009; UA001.018.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
    - Fares Center/Lecture, 2002; UA001.018.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
    - Fares Lecture, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
    - Fares Lecture, 2003; UA001.018.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
    - Fares, 2007; UA001.018.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
    - Leila Fawaz, 2009; UA001.018.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
    - Feinstein International Famine Center, 2005; UA001.018.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
    - Financial Management Network, 2008; UA001.018.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
    - Financial Aid, 2010; UA001.018.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
    - Fletcher Campus Visit, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.005393 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Ford Motor Company, 2003; UA001.018.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
    - FORSYTH, 2001; UA001.018.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
    - Foundation for Individual Rights in Education, Inc. (FIRE), 2010; UA001.018.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
    - Foundations of Leadership, 2008; UA001.018.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
    - Fraternities and Sororities, 2003; UA001.018.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
    - James Freedman, 2003 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
    - Friedman School Accreditation, 2009 -- 2011; UA001.005395 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, 2000 -- 2010; UA001.005394 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Freshman Advisees Photographs, 2001 -- 2002; UA001.018.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
    - Fulbright Association, 2007; UA001.018.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
    - Fulbright Scholar 2010-2011, UA001.005396 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Full Moon, 2011; UA001.018.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
    - Gabriela Steier- Drawing, Always a Jumbo at Heart, 2007; UA001.018.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
    - Gates Millennium Scholars, 2011; UA001.005397 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - GDAE, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
    - General Counsel's Office, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
    - Ghana VISA Request Sep 2010, UA001.005398 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - GI Bill Improvements, 2007; UA001.018.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
    - Global Appeal 2011 End Stigma and Discrimination against people affected by Leprosy, 2010 -- 2011; UA001.005399 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - GLSEN, 2004; UA001.018.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
    - Good Life Productions- Somerville Homeless Coalition Tribute to Bacow, 2011; UA001.018.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
      - Somerville Homeless Coalition - Tribute to Tufts University President Lawrence Bacow, 2011-04-23; UA001.018.001.004.00054.00001 (Box 4)
    - Gordon Institute, 2009; UA001.018.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
    - Bernie Gordon Project, 2005 -- 2006; UA001.018.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
    - Al Gore, 2002; UA001.018.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - Government Relations, 2011; UA001.018.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
    - Graduate Student Council, 2004; UA001.018.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - Graduate Education Council, 2003; UA001.018.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - Grants miscellaneous, 2009 -- 2011; UA001.005400 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce, 2003 -- 2010; UA001.005401 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Green Line, 2004 -- 2006; UA001.005402 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Hallmark Health, 2003; UA001.018.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - John Hancock, 2009; UA001.018.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology, 2007; UA001.018.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - Hong Kong, 2010; UA001.018.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Human Nutrition Research Center, 2010; UA001.018.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Health Sciences Campus Institutional Review Board, 2011; UA001.005403 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Health Sciences Library, 2001; UA001.018.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Health Services, 2010; UA001.018.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - HEI Subcommittee Reports, 1997 -- 1998; UA001.018.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - High Table Dinners, 2002 -- 2005; UA001.018.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Higher Education Cabinet, 2008; UA001.018.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Higher Education Initiative, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.018.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Hillel, 2007; UA001.018.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Hillel Board, 2009; UA001.018.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Holiday Cards 2002, 2002 -- 2003; UA001.005404 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Holiday Card 2004, UA001.005406 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - President's Holiday Parties 2003, UA001.005405 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - President's Holiday Parties and Card 2005, UA001.005407 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - President's Holiday Parties and Card 2006, UA001.005408 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - President's Holiday Parties and Cards 2007, UA001.005409 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - President's Holiday Parties and Cards 2008, UA001.005410 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Holiday Party 2009, UA001.005411 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Holiday Party 2010, 2001 -- 2010; UA001.005412 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1992 -- 2009; UA001.005413 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 2010; UA001.018.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - IDEAS Boston, 2011; UA001.005414 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - IES Minority Achievement Scholarship, 2009; UA001.018.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
    - Inaugurations, 2002 -- 2011; UA001.005415 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Inauguration Brochures, 2002; UA001.018.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
    - Inauguration Correspondence and Thank You Notes (1 of 4), 2001; UA001.018.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
    - Inauguration Correspondence and Thank You Notes (2 of 4), 2001; UA001.018.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
    - Inauguration Correspondence and Thank You Notes (3 of 4), 2001; UA001.018.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
    - Inauguration Correspondence and Thank You Notes (4 of 4), 2001; UA001.018.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
    - Inner-City Scholarship Fund, 2001 -- 2010; UA001.005416 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Inquiries to President's office miscellaneous, 2009 -- 2011; UA001.005417 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Institutional Research, 2006; UA001.018.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
    - Institute for Global Leadership, 2009; UA001.018.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
    - Institute of Medicine and National Academy of Engineering, 2011; UA001.005418 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - International Association of University Presidents, 2001 -- 2010; UA001.005419 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - International Relations Program, 2007; UA001.018.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
    - Investment Committee, 2001 -- 2009; UA001.005422 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Invitations from President Bacow miscellaneous, 2010 -- 2011; UA001.005420 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Islamic Center, 2001 -- 2006; UA001.005421 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Israel Boycott, 2007; UA001.018.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
    - iTours, 2005; UA001.018.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
    - Jumbo Club, 2005; UA001.018.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
    - Jumpstart, 2010; UA001.018.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
    - Kagan Associates, 2004; UA001.018.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
    - Kennedy, 2003 -- 2009; UA001.018.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
    - Kids to College, 2006; UA001.018.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
    - Killam Fellowships Program, 2004; UA001.018.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
    - Martin Luther King, 2006; UA001.018.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
    - Ben Kincannon, 2001; UA001.018.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
    - Kluge Prize Nomination July 2011, UA001.005423 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Korea, 2008; UA001.018.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
    - Louis Lasagna, 2002; UA001.018.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
    - Larry Bacow new hire form, signature, key request, head shots 2004, 2001 -- 2004; UA001.005424 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Lawrence Memorial Hospital, 2005; UA001.018.001.005.00041 (Box 5)
    - Leadership Alliance, 2005; UA001.018.001.005.00042 (Box 5)
    - Leadership Retreat, 2004; UA001.018.001.005.00043 (Box 5)
    - Leontief Prize, 2007; UA001.018.001.005.00044 (Box 5)
    - Life Sciences Collaborative 2010, UA001.005425 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - LGBTQ, 2010; UA001.005426 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Light on the Hill Award January 2011, UA001.005427 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Louis Stokes Alliance for Minority Participation, 2010; UA001.005428 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Nelson Mandela, 2007; UA001.018.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Daniel Mandell, 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Marathon, 2008; UA001.018.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Marathon, 2003; UA001.018.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Marathon, 2004; UA001.018.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Marathon, 2005; UA001.018.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
    - Marathon, 2006; UA001.018.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Marathon, 2007; UA001.018.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, 2008; UA001.018.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
    - Marts & Lundy, 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
    - Mass Consortium for Biomedical Research, 2006; UA001.018.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
    - Mass Insight Report, 2009; UA001.018.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
    - MA Coaltion for Authentic Reform in Education, 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
    - Massachusetts Campus Compact, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.005429 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts Electric (2002 Power outage), UA001.018.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
    - Massachusetts Life Sciences Collaborative, 2009; UA001.018.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
    - Massachusetts Renewable Energy Trust, 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
    - Massachusetts Service Alliance, 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
    - Mass Science and Technology Coalition, 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
    - Master Plan, 2005; UA001.018.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
    - Matriculation, 2009; UA001.018.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
    - Jean Mayer, 2006; UA001.018.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
    - Medical Education for South African Blacks (MESAB), 2003; UA001.018.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
    - Medical School, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.005430 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Medical School Dean Search, 2002 -- 2003; UA001.005431 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Medical School Health Sciences Issues, 2001; UA001.018.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
    - Melberger Award, 2002; UA001.005432 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health, 2004; UA001.018.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
    - MIT150 Infinite History Project, 2008 -- 2010; UA001.005433 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Bill Moomaw, 2003; UA001.018.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
    - Muhimbili University of Health & Allied Sciences (MUHAS), 2009; UA001.018.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
    - Museum of Science, 2005; UA001.018.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
    - Museum School, 2007; UA001.018.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
    - Music, 2007; UA001.018.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
    - Music Building, 2008; UA001.018.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
    - NACME (National Action Council for Minorities in Eng.), 2009; UA001.018.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
    - NAICU, 2011; UA001.018.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
    - National Council for Science and the Environment, 2009; UA001.018.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
    - National College Health Improvement Project 2011, UA001.005434 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 2011; UA001.018.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
    - National Research Council, 2006; UA001.018.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), 2010; UA001.018.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
    - NCAA, 2011; UA001.018.001.006.00037 (Box 6)
    - NCAA - Intitutional Self-Study, 1998; UA001.018.001.006.00038 (Box 6)
    - Miriam Nelson, 2001; UA001.018.001.006.00039 (Box 6)
    - Nerd Girls, 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00040 (Box 6)
    - NEASC -5 YR Interim Report, 1997; UA001.018.001.006.00041 (Box 6)
    - NEASC Nov 2010, UA001.005435 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - NESCAC, 2001 -- 2002; UA001.018.001.006.00042 (Box 6)
    - NESCAC, 2002 -- 2003; UA001.018.001.006.00043 (Box 6)
    - NESCAC Reaccreditation, 2003; UA001.018.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
    - NESCAC, 2003 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
    - NESCAC (1 of 2), 2004 -- 2007; UA001.018.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
    - NESCAC (2 of 2), 2004 -- 2007; UA001.018.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
    - NESCAC 2007, 2007 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
    - New England Board of Higher Education, 2003 -- 2008; UA001.018.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
    - New England Resource Center for Higher Education, 2001 -- 2003; UA001.018.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
    - Newton, Isaac Apple Tree at Tufts, 2011; UA001.005436 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Nice Letters, 2001 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
    - Nippon Foundation, 2010; UA001.018.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
    - Nominations, 2011; UA001.018.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
    - Nominations, 2004 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
    - Northeastern University, 2004 -- 2006; UA001.018.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
    - NROTC, 2002 -- 2008; UA001.018.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
    - Office of Equal Opportunity, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
    - Olin College Visit, 2003 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
    - Omidayr Scholars, 2002 -- 2003; UA001.018.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
    - Open Courseware, 2005 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
    - Open Courseware Initiative (OKI), 2002 -- 2005; UA001.018.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
    - Outdoor Sculpture, 2004; UA001.018.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
    - Oversight Panel Task Force on Race implementation of recommendations 2000-2001, UA001.005437 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Oversight Panel for the Task Force, 2001 -- 2002; UA001.018.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
    - Elsa U. Pardee Foundation, 2002 -- 2003; UA001.018.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
    - Parent Letters, 1999 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
    - Parents Committee, 2002 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
    - Parents Weekend, 2001; UA001.018.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
    - Parents Weekend, 2004; UA001.018.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
    - Partnership for Public Service, 2008; UA001.018.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
    - Patches for Peace, 2001; UA001.018.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
    - Payment in Lieu of Tax PILOT, 2009 -- 2010; UA001.005438 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Peace Corps, 2002 -- 2008; UA001.018.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
    - Pepsico, 2003 -- 2005; UA001.018.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
    - Pew Charitable Trust, 2010 -- 2011; UA001.005439 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Phi Betta Kappa Society, 2002 -- 2006; UA001.018.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
    - Physics and Astronomy, 2002 -- 2007; UA001.018.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
    - Prague - April 24 - 29, 2011, 2001; UA001.018.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
    - President Bacow's Video Message to the Board of Trustees, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.018.001.007.00033
    - President Search, 2001; UA001.018.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
    - Presidential Awards, 2008 -- 2010; UA001.018.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
    - Presidential Awards, 2007; UA001.018.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
    - Presidential Award for Citizenship and Public Service, 2003; UA001.018.001.007.00037 (Box 7)
    - Presidential Award for Citizenship and Public Service, 2004; UA001.018.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - Presidential Award for Citizenship and Public Service, 2005; UA001.018.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Presidential Review Committee, 2006; UA001.018.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Presidential Symposium, 2005; UA001.018.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
      - Presidential Symposium, 2005; UA001.018.001.008.00004.00001
    - President's Office, 2005; UA001.018.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Presidents Climate Commitment, 2007; UA001.018.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - Prez Award for Citizenship and Public Service, 2006; UA001.018.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
    - Price Waterhouse Coopers, 2007; UA001.018.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
    - Primary Source, 2001 -- 2008; UA001.018.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - Princeton Forum, 2007; UA001.018.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
    - Princeton Review, 2003 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
    - Programs Abroad, 2001 -- 2011; UA001.005440 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Provost Search 2001-02, 1999 -- 2002; UA001.005441 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - PT Barnum Award June 2011, UA001.005442 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Public Relations, 2007; UA001.018.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
      - Study Abroad in the U.S.A. - Promotional Video for Chinese Students, 2007; UA001.018.001.008.00012.00001
    - Public Safety, 2008; UA001.018.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
    - Publications, 2006; UA001.018.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
    - Quarter Century Club, 2006; UA001.018.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
    - RAPIT, 2002; UA001.018.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
    - Read by the River, 2002; UA001.018.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
    - REAL Program, 2009; UA001.018.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
    - Recommendations, 2001 -- 2005; UA001.018.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
    - Recommendations (1 of 2), 2011; UA001.018.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
    - Recommendations (2 of 2), 2009; UA001.018.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
    - Regrets, 2011; UA001.018.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
    - Requests, 2011; UA001.018.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
    - Research, 2003; UA001.018.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
    - Resumes, 2009; UA001.018.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
    - Resumes, 2001 -- 2005; UA001.018.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
    - Retiree Medical Plan, 2003; UA001.018.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
    - ROTC, 2011; UA001.018.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
    - Royall House, 2002; UA001.005443 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Sackler, 2008; UA001.018.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
    - Sackler Dean, 2001 -- 2004; UA001.005444 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Jeswald W. Salacuse, 2003; UA001.018.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
    - SARS, 2003; UA001.018.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
    - Say Yes, 2009; UA001.018.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
    - School of Dental Medicine Appreciation, 2011; UA001.018.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
    - School of Dental Medicine Faculty Congratulations, 2002; UA001.018.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
    - School of Medicine Basic Science Chairs, 2002; UA001.018.001.008.00035 (Box 8)
    - Science Coalition, 2006; UA001.018.001.008.00036 (Box 8)
    - Science Coalition - Appropriation Letters, 2002; UA001.018.001.008.00037 (Box 8)
    - Science and Technology Center, 2007; UA001.018.001.008.00038 (Box 8)
    - Science and Technology in Society 2011, 2010 -- 2011; UA001.005445 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Science Training Encouraging Peace STEP, 2010; UA001.005446 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Scrolls, 2002; UA001.018.001.008.00039 (Box 8)
    - Senior Dinners, 2003 -- 2004; UA001.018.001.008.00040 (Box 8)
    - Senior Dinners, 2006; UA001.018.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
    - September 11, 2001, 2001 -- 2002; UA001.018.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
    - Seraph Foundation, Inc., 2002; UA001.018.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
    - Service Nation, 2008; UA001.018.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
    - Sesquicentennial Planning Binder, Book 1, Part 1 of 3, 2001; UA001.018.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
    - Sesquicentennial Planning Binder, Book 1, Part 2 of 3, 2001; UA001.018.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
    - Sesquicentennial Planning Binder, Book 1, Part 3 of 3, 2001; UA001.018.001.009.00007 (Box 9)